<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TVshows on Consulting Statistician</title>
    <link>/tags/tvshows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TVshows on Consulting Statistician</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/tvshows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Shows</title>
      <link>/projects/tvshows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/tvshows/</guid>
      <description>More than 50 TV shows are on my list and I have watched all of them. There are alot of shows in this list where all would agree be great and enticing. There is no specific genre of my interest and I do not mind re-watching these TV shows again.
0 to 9  1983 24  A  A bit of Fry and Laurie After life Altered Carbon Archer Asian Provocateur Alias   B  Band of Brothers Barry Big Train Black Mirror Blue Planet I,II BodyGuard BroadChurch Brooklynn Nine Nine Boston Legal  C  Chance Chernobyl Collateral Condor Cosmos A space time odyssey Community Criminal : UK  D  Dynasties Doctor Who Derry Girls  E  Episodes Entourage  F  Family Guy Fawlty Towers Fleabag Friends Frasier  G  Gadget Man Game of Thrones Good Omens Goodness Gracious Me Gangs of London  H  House House of Cards US House of Cards UK How I Met Your Mother Harley Quinn Hunters  I  Informer Inside Edge  J  Jeeves and Wooster Jessica Jones Johnny Bravo  K  Key and Peele Killing Eve Koombiyo Keeping Up Appearances  L  Line of Duty Love, Death and Robots Luther Lucifer Last week tonight with John Oliver  M  Manhunt Master of None Monty Python The Flying Circus Money Heist Mindhunter Mind Your Language Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>