<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Consulting Statistician</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Consulting Statistician</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Shows</title>
      <link>/projects/tvshows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/tvshows/</guid>
      <description>More than 50 TV shows are on my list and I have watched all of them. There are alot of shows in this list where all would agree be great and enticing. There is no specific genre of my interest and I do not mind re-watching these TV shows again.
0 to 9  1983 24  A  A bit of Fry and Laurie After life Altered Carbon Archer Asian Provocateur   B  Band of Brothers Barry Big Train Black Mirror Blue Planet I,II BodyGuard BroadChurch Brooklynn Nine Nine  C  Chance Chernobyl Collateral Condor Cosmos A space time odyssey  D  Dynasties Doctor Who  E  Episodes  F  Family Guy Fawlty Towers Fleabag Friends  G  Gadget Man Game of Thrones Good Omens Goodness Gracious Me  H  House House of Cards US House of Cards UK How I Met Your Mother  I  Informer  J  Jeeves and Wooster Jessica Jones Johnny Bravo  K  Key and Peele Killing Eve Koombiyo  L  Line of Duty Love, Death and Robots Luther  M  Manhunt Master of None Monty Python The Flying Circus Money Heist Mindhunter Mind Your Language Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books I have read</title>
      <link>/projects/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/books/</guid>
      <description>I started reading books from month of April, 2018. Which is very useful for my life as a believer of self-learning. I hope to share these books with you so that it will be useful. There is no meaning in numbers except that they are just for ordering from 1 to further in no hierarchy. Genre specificity is not my thing therefore these books are not divided into groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies</title>
      <link>/projects/movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/movies/</guid>
      <description>Watching movies for the last six years(from 2012) with much interest in plot, story line and characters. I have watched more than 300 movies but the below mentioned are in my mind. They are from different decades as well, therefore do not hesistate to watch. If you prefer go through the IMDB link so that the ratings and summary will give you more information.
0 to 9  12 Angry Men 13 Hours The Secret Soldiers of Benghazi 2012  A  A Private War American Gangster Aquaman Arrival Asterix and Obelix Mansion of Gods Asterix and Obelix The Secret of The Magic Potion Avengers Trilogy Argo  B  Bad Boys Dualogy Batman Trilogy Between Two Ferns The Movie Black Hawk Down Black Panther BlacKkKlansman Bohemian Rhaspody Bridge of Spies  C  Captain America Trilogy Captain Marvel Casablanca Captive State Casino Chaos Charlie Brown Charlie Chaplin Modern Times Charlie Wilsons War Constantine Cast Away  D  Deadpool Dualogy Deja Vu Doctor Strange Dan Brown Trilogy Die Hard Quadropolgy Despicable Me Collection Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>