<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Consulting Statistician</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Consulting Statistician</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Books I have read</title>
      <link>/projects/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/books/</guid>
      <description>I started reading books from month of April, 2018. Which is very useful for my life as a believer of self-learning. I hope to share these books with you so that it will be useful. There is no meaning in numbers except that they are just for ordering from 1 to further in no hierarchy. Genre specificity is not my thing therefore these books are not divided into groups.
 Rise the Dark by Michael Koryta The Bourne Enigma by Eric Van LustBader Jack Reacher thriller, A Wanted Man by Lee Child Digital Fortress by Dan Brown The Selfish Gene by Richard Dawkins How Democracies Die by Steven Levitsky and Daniel Ziblatt Elon Musk by Ashlee Vance Roll of Thunder Hear My Cry by Mildred Taylor Boy by Roald Dohl Animal Farm by George Orwell The power of Habit by Charles Duhigg  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies</title>
      <link>/projects/movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/movies/</guid>
      <description>Watching movies for the last six years(from 2012) with much interest in plot, story line and characters. I have watched more than 300 movies but the below mentioned are in my mind. They are from different decades as well, therefore do not hesistate to watch. If you prefer go through the IMDB link so that the ratings and summary will give you more information. 36 Movies will be mentioned below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Shows</title>
      <link>/projects/tvshows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/tvshows/</guid>
      <description>More than 50 TV shows are on my list and I have watched all of them. There are alot of shows in this list where all would agree be great and enticing. There is no specific genre of my interest and I do not mind rewatching these TV shows again.
 [1983]() A bit of Fry and Laurie Altered Carbon Band of Brothers [Barry]() Black Mirror Blue Planet I,II [BodyGuard]() BroadChurch Barry Brookynn Nine Nine Chance Condor Cosmos A space time odyssey [Dynasties]() Doctor Who Fawlty Towers Friends House House of Cards US House of Cards UK How I Met Your Mother Jeeves and Wooster Killing Eve [Koombiyo]() Line of Duty Luther [Manhunt]() Monty Python The Flying Circus [Mindhunter]() Mind Your Language Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>